Is it true?
Netanyahu deceased?
Benjamin Netanyahu deceased?
Let's just talk about some things real quick.
Hamadi, you cannot do that.
Don't say it's not true and then not give reasons why it's not true.
And also don't come with it's part of the plan.
Sometimes y'all give these people way too much credit.
You seem to think that they cannot be fallible.
And I just want you to know that that is the indoctrination working.
Of course, Google is saying it's false.
Okay, let's discuss some things.
One, he has not been seen.
Hold on, let me block this person.
He has not been seen in five days.
Two, he was seen in an AI video with a sixth finger.
That, that, that happened.
He was seen in an, in a, in a, in a, um, in a video with six fingers.
Now, someone on here just said, he's alive.
I will block you.
If you are going to counter a narrative,
state what proof you have to counter the narrative.
Now, he was not on the security briefing.
And if he, if he isn't deceased, he's definitely compromised.
Because that type of arrogance,
that type of megalomaniacal maniac,
you don't like get quiet.
If you saw the interview recently that was happening with, um,
one of Trump's little cronies,
he was in the interview.
In the middle of the interview,
he was pulled out.
Then,
Sabir on.
hold on, y'all know I always got food in my teeth.
And it's always spinach.
Because I eat spinach with every meal.
Then,
they brought Buddy back into the meeting.
I'm going to show y'all how the interview was before.
All right?
It was lit.
I'm not exaggerating.
It was like this.
Right.
Yeah.
Well,
you know.
Oh.
I have to.
I'll be,
I'll be back.
Five minutes later.
Um,
um,
I love my son.
I really,
I really love my children.
Um,
my children are,
the cats meow.
Am I wrong?
Was that not what happened?
Talking about his children.
That man,
his kids.
Talking about,
I love my children.
Right?
And so,
people were watching this,
and they were like,
you know,
it feels like he's mentioning his kids,
because that would be the first thing that comes to mind when you feel like you have crossed the Rubicon.
Anyone here know what crossing the Rubicon means?
Okay,
so it was the U.S. Treasury Secretary,
Scott Besant.
And for what it's worth,
the U.S. Treasury Secretary,
Scott Besant actually be like,
kind of clowning Trump.
Um,
okay,
so cross the Rubicon means no turning back.
so Caesar,
when he was invading,
Rome,
I think,
um,
it was like,
all right,
once you let us cross this Rubicon,
it's a Rizzy Rizzy.
And,
the Rubicon was crossed,
and it was a rap Rizzy.
So anytime you hear someone say,
they've crossed the Rubicon,
it's like the war version of,
they've jumped the shark.
There's no turning back.
They done pulled the trigger.
You can also say,
there's also the term like,
burning your ships.
Because when you burn your ships,
that's what the Armadas used to do.
They would burn their ships,
and go into the,
the fight.
Because,
if you burn your ships,
baby,
all you can do is,
is,
is take the other people's ships.
How to understand something,
that I feel like people,
have been grappling with.
I saw someone say the other day,
I hate celebrating war.
And I think it's really important to understand,
celebrating balance.
If we understand nature,
we understand balance.
We understand that there are predators and prey.
And we understand that even though,
you don't necessarily want to see a soul gone,
that the balance of that,
the circle of life,
if you will,
is necessary for the harmony of the universe,
and the harmony of the ecosystem,
and of the planet.
We,
as humans,
have completely dislodged from harmony.
Completely.
And,
the reality is,
some people gotta die,
for harmony to be restored.
The same way you got to pull weeds,
to protect your garden.
The same way you have to deter,
vermin.
The same way you have to,
eradicate,
pests.
You can always look to nature,
to understand and to see,
okay,
am I bugging?
So,
when we hear people say things like,
you know,
an eye for an eye,
makes the world blind.
First of all,
that was said by Gandhi,
who absolutely,
was not somebody,
that you should be quoting.
He was a bleeding heart racist,
and,
he was a PDF.
So,
let's stop with that.
Second,
he was working in cahoots with the colonizers.
So,
him saying an eye for an eye,
makes the world blind,
supported his pacifist ideologies,
which by the way,
Martin Luther King was following,
only to realize,
god dang,
we was pacifists,
and then people was passing,
a fist,
into our faces.
Into our faces.
Right?
So,
the pacifism nonsense,
is not in,
it's not even practical in nature.
Okay?
It's not even practical in nature.
Gandhi was literally in there,
with Churchill,
talking about partition.
You know how many people died,
during partition,
and the creation of Pakistan?
You think it's a coincidence,
that they're doing this war during Ramadan?
Do you think that's a coincidence?
They thought these people,
in it on,
were going to be too hungry to fight.
That their brains wouldn't be as sharp.
Because these people,
they do not understand believing in something,
that is actually of life.
They don't understand that,
because what they believe in is destruction.
So they can't conceptualize,
that you would be during Ramadan,
that you would be physically hungry,
but mentally strong.
They can't conceptualize that.
Like,
literally,
soldiers would,
fast during Ramadan,
together,
to prepare,
for battle.
Ramadan almost over though.
Ramadan almost over.
That's why they thought,
oh,
we're going to handle this in two weeks.
No.
We have to also always remember,
to give,
to give dua,
to give thank you,
to give praises,
to those whose lives are being sacrificed,
for the world to be better.
Do you know that?
They're not the first,
they're not the last,
but they are the now.
And you should be lifting them up every day.
I was literally sitting here,
writing a song,
about,
I was literally,
literally writing a song,
about,
it's gotta be a better way,
we've gotta make it,
to create it,
the same old road,
how long,
I know when we,
it's gotta be a better way,
we've gotta create it,
we've got to,
people are asking,
well,
what do you think Izzy's gonna do,
if homeboy's dead?
You know,
I think something that people need to really understand,
is that,
you know,
he is not,
how do I put it?
He's not a mastermind,
he is a,
willing participant,
of the advancement,
of destruction,
and,
he did not create that,
it will not end with him,
it's the same with Donald Trump,
I'll keep talking about other people on my songs,
and I don't know why,
I don't see nobody else on these songs,
but me,
so,
um,
it's not England,
it's,
it's the World Bank,
and the Central Bank,
England was how,
the Roman Empire continued,
but,
then it was America,
and then it was,
it's trying to be,
oh,
thanks,
Efemir,
um,
and now it's trying to be Israel,
but the mistake that y'all,
make so often,
is this feeling,
that these people are infallible,
like they don't make errors,
you know,
it's this feeling like they are just so incredible,
and that they cannot be checked,
they cannot be defeated,
and the problem is that they believe that too,
so,
you're gonna have to,
start believing in yourself,
because that's the other thing,
when you believe that,
you let yourself off the hook,
from trying to be,
a part of the solution,
you know that,
right,
every time that you spout rhetoric,
that suggests,
that these people,
are infallible,
that they are,
unable to be defeated,
um,
impervious,
you are subconsciously saying,
and thus,
I will not be expected,
to beat them,
even though you see proof,
all the time,
of their mediocrity,
the only reason,
they're where they are,
is because of the suppression,
of those,
who are connected,
to a greater power,
and that is the power of the earth,
and the spirits,
that's it,
there's gotta be a better way,
grow so long,
said there's gotta be a better way,
you got to create it,
when am I putting it out,
I literally just made it today,
so,
who knows,
y'all have talked me into,
putting together,
some type of like,
EP of some sort,
I've just been trying to think,
of what the name is,
and I would do an EP,
of the songs that I'd be making,
like,
in a day,
if ground troops come,
they about to be sacrificed,
yes,
you should always believe,
someone that,
should be scared of you,
and is not,
you should always believe them,
when,
okay,
like,
the fact that they like,
come through,
come through though,
come outside,
we just wanna talk,
just come outside,
I was telling my homegirls today,
the first time,
and the only time,
I've ever been in a physical fight,
was,
when,
I was told,
come outside,
we just wanna talk,
and I thought they just wanted to talk,
I agreed to wanna,
100%,
I thought they really just wanted to talk,
and so I came outside,
a fight ensued,
yeah,
we ain't gonna,
I definitely,
it,
it did not occur to me,
that I was about to get,
jumped,
that did not,
even faintly,
occur to me,
I'm like,
I'm in capris,
and sandals,
what,
I did win,
yes,
you know,
don't say I win,
I won because,
like,
she got pulled off,
and the next day,
it was my name,
that was going through the,
the text machines,
the,
the two-way pagers,
my homeboy,
Esco,
rest in peace,
texting was like,
yo,
I heard you got in a fight last night,
and you beat their ass,
correct,
if that's what you heard,
that's how it happened,
I really won,
because she was fighting me,
over a dude,
because I had said,
that,
because I,
I heard,
the story is longer,
but the,
the long and short of it,
is that,
I,
her friend told me,
she was dating my ex,
and I was like,
well just tell her,
be careful,
because he'd be lying,
about how many BMs he has,
and,
then,
she pops out,
and is offended,
that I was talking about her man,
and I was like,
but I,
I was trying to help you out,
like,
why are you mad at me,
and she was like,
keep my man name,
out your mouth,
and I like,
moved her hand,
and then she,
punched me in my face,
and I was like,
ah,
I think I was like,
probably about 25,
and so now,
we scrapping,
this is a much longer,
better story,
that I will tell one day,
on Patreon,
so then we're scrapping,
and people trying to pull us off,
I've got some of her hair,
in my hand,
and,
I say that I won,
because he broke up with her,
for fighting me,
and they called me the next day,
and said,
I am sorry that that happened,
that's fucked up,
and I was like,
he was like,
yeah,
that wasn't it,
I said,
you have to call my mom,
and tell her that you are sorry,
that your girl beat me up,
because of you,
he did,
he called my mom,
and said,
I'm sorry,
Ms. Seals,
the ancestors are always,
protecting me,
always,
and then,
I remember like,
maybe like two months later,
I went to a premiere,
of a movie,
like at,
like ANC,
on 42nd street,
and she was there,
on like,
a BS red carpet,
with a mic,
trying to be,
an influencer,
like trying to interview people,
I said,
oh you,
look at you trying to be,
what I already am,
that's cute,
look at you trying to be,
what I'm already done doing,
adorbs,
adorbs nation,
what do you mean,
I grew up in New York,
I was 26,
25,
26,
when this happened,
um,
it's gotta be a better way,
someone asked,
what do we do on Patreon,
Nancy,
send me a picture,
of the baby please,
um,
what do we do on Patreon,
we have,
you said that's mean,
no,
punching me in my face,
over a nigga is mean,
me saying the honest truth,
is actually just,
petty,
mean,
um,
but,
Patreon,
uh,
what do we do on Patreon,
well,
we do Zooms,
we do lives,
um,
I also,
post exclusive content,
over there,
on Patreon,
um,
they have a book club,
that they run,
um,
the community runs,
and,
we do,
we do exclusive interviews,
with the authors,
um,
what else,
oh,
you won't wake me up,
Nelsie,
you will not wake me up,
I be out,
like a light,
but gracias,
um,
the biggest thing,
that you do at Patreon,
is you support my work,
that's the biggest thing,
you support,
you know,
you get,
that's the biggest thing,
okay,
you gotta be,
we say,
we share pet photos,
oh,
that's the other thing,
our chats,
we have chats on Patreon,
in my Patreon,
the Seal Squad,
that are really just robust,
with information,
on,
like,
current events,
there's another chat for gardening,
there's another chat for socialism,
and learning about socialism,
there's another chat for learning about Zionism,
there's another chat for,
um,
the book club,
there's a whole other chat for our pets,
um,
and then,
the lives,
yep,
the link is in my bio,
and then I would say,
the lives on Patreon,
are also different,
because it's a community,
and like,
people know each other,
at this point,
like,
we've been,
on this,
some of them have been on there for years,
so there's a,
um,
there's a,
what's the word I'm looking for,
y'all,
there's a rapport,
there's a comfort,
um,
and you,
you get more insight into,
you get to see more of my life,
um,
I do,
uh,
travel,
it's become a travel series,
called Behind the Seals,
and,
um,
you see the full episodes of that,
so,
do I open the Zooms?
Yeah,
we do Zooms on Wednesdays,
um,
after Views for Amanda Land,
and then even after I finish,
even after I stop doing Views for Amanda Land on March 25th,
we'll continue to do Zooms,
um,
so,
you know,
it's just,
um,
and it's a super diverse group,
and I think that's really special,
it's diverse in gender,
it's diverse in class,
it's diverse in race,
it's diverse in location,
I mean,
all the things,
thank you,
Ducks and Tigers,
I'm working on that tonight as well,
sigh,
yeah,
I should bring that into my,
um,
it's all the sigh,
produce these on my phone,
you know,
I've got my phone like,
ooh,
that sounds cool together,
um,
so,
anywho,
yeah,
I wanted to pop in,
because I'm hoping that the truth is that,
BB has left,
the planet,
um,
but you know,
it could be a sigh,
yeah,
sigh,
can't believe nothing,
cause they've been frightened,
okay,
I am gonna go back on Twitch,
if I'm honest,
I'd be like,
yeah,
Views for Manland is ending on March 25th,
Twitch like scares me,
it's like so involved,
and I'd be like,
I know that the more I do it,
the less it will feel that way,
but,
I'm just like,
so,
I know that I need to be more over there,
so I'm going to do it,
I'm going to do it,
not tonight,
but I'm gonna do it,
I don't even know what kick is,
y'all be like,
why not,
y'all will name apps,
be like,
you'll be like,
why not,
um,
I don't know,
why not Fishfoot instead,
I'm like,
I don't know what Fishfoot.com is,
I don't know what that is,
I don't,
who is BB,
damn,
I just want to show y'all,
this is my sweater I was wearing today,
and I've been hitting y'all with the sweaters all week,
but Jordy has made,
mind you,
his bed is there,
but he said,
no,
I'm gonna be,
I'm gonna be here,
I hope y'all see how dope the sweater is,
by the way,
Ducks and Tigers,
don't be sad,
be appreciative that it happened at all,
I made that show from nothing,
my radio show was canceled on a Tuesday,
and I created Views for a Mandalorian by Monday,
and what I realized is that I've been working out of reaction,
not intention,
I do not want to be an influencer,
I do not want to be a talking head,
there are people who take great joy in doing that,
and who that is also their calling,
in a way that it's not mine,
Sabby Sab,
Brianna Joy Gray,
I need to be making music,
and making art,
oh,
thanks to Fat Man,
that means a lot,
Tawana said,
let's get the Psy Off song out,
y'all,
I need y'all to understand,
that y'all are the funniest people ever,
y'all,
like,
the people who end up on my lives,
whether it's Patreon,
whether it's YouTube,
like,
yeah,
I really attract funny folks,
it took years,
join Native Land Pod,
why would I join that,
why,
why would I join Native Land Pod,
you tell me,
see what I will gain,
size,
see Jamal said,
a headache,
okay,
facts,
factory,
yeah,
it's on a side,
oh,
but I am a talking head,
but I am,
if it looks like a duck,
and it walks like a duck,
it doesn't matter,
if it's a goose,
it will be treated like a duck,
not better than a chicken head,
you know,
how do I live semi-peacefully,
I just,
I am consistently,
in pursuit of whimsy,
and,
in exploration of the self,
to be in more connection with,
the spirit,
of the earth,
and,
I'm also neurodivergent,
so,
my brain,
works in,
like,
in mysterious ways,
honestly,
I'm not the best person,
to talk to about that,
I think sometimes,
people mistake me,
for someone like,
Ben Crump,
or Sean King,
or,
you know,
Tamika Mallory,
and,
you know,
I'm not,
I'm stimming right now,
I'm not a,
I'm not an organizer,
and,
I'm not,
I'm an advocate,
however,
I'm not,
I am not,
I'm,
I'm not the person,
who,
I'm not,
you know,
like,
when Al Sharpton would show at places,
that,
that's,
I'm an artist,
and so I'm best,
I'm best at making art,
who is Jamal Bryant,
and why is he trying to end the target boycott,
well,
if you're,
if you're being wrongly,
if you're in jail wrongly,
then you should be speaking to a,
a civil rights attorney,
um,
where are you incarcerated,
Miss Leos,
you saw me stimming,
that's like,
oh,
yeah,
yep,
I am P45,
in California,
that,
um,
I know that's incarcerated right now,
that is working on,
this same scenario,
so I'm gonna see who they can,
um,
refer me to,
and I will DM you,
does that sound cool?
Hold your head,
keep it low,
keep yourself clean,
if I'm being honest,
I've been very,
self-conscious about my singing voice,
in my recording,
like,
I feel like when I sing like this,
I like it,
and then when I hear it back,
I don't like it,
so I'm having to really work through that,
so I'm just being honest,
okay,
that's enough honesty,
um,
may the world be rid of,
destructive,
energies,
there's no vocals on the track,
that's just like a,
that was just like a reference,
there's no vocals on the track,
I haven't even made the track,
like,
that's just like the,
that's just,
it's called a stack,
where you like stack a bunch of samples,
so I haven't even,
like,
turned it into an actual track,
I was working on the other song,
because I have,
a shirt,
that I designed,
that says,
we can't vote our way out of evil,
and so,
I wanted to write this song,
to go along with that,
but for what it's worth,
you all,
I literally have enough tracks for an EP,
like I,
I'm going to Cuba on Thursday,
but,
I'm trying to actually get a bunch of shit done,
so I can actually do this,
what's my take on Malcolm X saying,
it's the ballot or the bullet,
you know,
you know what I just learned today,
that Kwanzaa was created by Milana Karenga,
Ron Karenga,
that's not true apparently,
apparently Ron Karenga was an op,
that was planted at UCLA,
to infiltrate the Panthers,
ultimately got,
Bunchy Carter,
and,
I forgot who the other brother's name was,
Merked,
by the feds,
and as a thank you for that,
they said,
alright,
we gonna give y'all this thing,
and you get to have the name,
as the creator,
so literally Kwanzaa,
according to these two ex-Panthers,
who were talking about it,
Kwanzaa is a PSYOP,
and if we keep it honest,
like,
why would we be celebrating,
anything during that time of year,
if we're people of the planet,
people of the earth,
that's some Gregorian nonsense,
PSYOP,
it's,
it's all a PSYOP,
and I'm gonna post the video,
you know how some people be talking,
and you don't believe them,
because you're like,
you doing too much,
they not,
you know what Sarah,
you ain't never goddamn lie,
damn,
you ain't never lie Sarah,
shit,
should have known,
when they was letting us celebrate it in school,
PSYOP,
his son of PSYOP,
can't believe nothing,
because they stay fri-ing,
and they gon' lie to you,
PSYOP stands for psychological operation,
it is a concerted and planned effort of manipulation,
to distort truths,
to affect a response,
or to assert a response,
yep,
Iron Camellia,
apparently,
because then they also added,
they were like,
they didn't want black people celebrating Christmas,
they wanted us to have like,
do y'all's own thing over there,
so Michelle,
a PSYOP,
in my opinion,
is the 92%,
that's a PSYOP,
throwing that number out there,
and creating division,
right,
it is a,
it is a decisive,
tactical tool,
that is disseminated amongst the people,
to invoke a response,
that can be utilized,
for repression,
suppression,
or whatever they want,
so like,
I believe the 92% is a PSYOP,
because one,
why,
yes,
propaganda is a PSYOP,
because,
why would there be,
a number,
thrown out,
that's positive for black women,
by mainstream media,
other than to use black women,
furthermore,
mainstream media,
are literally,
the big PSYOP,
so,
any number,
any number they give you,
you should be side eyeing,
you should pass that number,
right on back,
okay,
and,
third,
you know,
the concept of the 92%,
still has you being proud,
to vote for a genocider,
so,
it's still,
like,
cut it out,
someone said,
Boosie is a PSYOP,
Iron Camila,
you haven't heard of the 92%,
Google it,
Google that,
it's black women,
who,
identify themselves,
as voters for Kamala,
because,
apparently,
the media said,
that 92% of black women,
voted for Kamala,
and so,
this became a stamp of pride,
that,
you know,
black women did what we were supposed to do,
and then the other side of that became,
and thus,
black women,
you know,
will not be involved,
in fighting back against ICE,
I genuinely don't even know who Jamal Bryant is,
it went from,
you voted for the lesser of two evils,
to like,
I'm proud of who I voted for,
and that's crazy,
you said you want,
wow,
you're in Sri Lanka,
that's cool,
he's nobody,
okay,
no Charlene,
I stopped doing small doses last year,
eight years,
I did small doses podcast,
but,
I got a special,
eighth anniversary small doses shirt,
with all 400 episodes on the back,
for sale at my store,
Amanda Land Exports,
you can get my book,
What Would the Ancestors Say,
you can get,
you can get a,
how black am I gonna have to get,
notebook,
oh man,
okay,
there you go,
you guys,